<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://www.prs.wiki/blog</id>
    <title>Peter R. Spackman Blog</title>
    <updated>2022-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.prs.wiki/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Peter R. Spackman Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://www.prs.wiki/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle]]></title>
        <id>wordle</id>
        <link href="https://www.prs.wiki/blog/wordle"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle is a simple, elegant]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.powerlanguage.co.uk/wordle/">Wordle</a> is a simple, elegant
word game which has become massively popular, at least on twitter.</p><p>So far, the author hasn&#x27;t commercialized it, and the social aspect
of comparing your performance for the same puzzle to others every day
clearly hits on something very appealing.</p><p>As when any puzzle gets popular, there has been lots of discussion around
wordle solvers. You might think &quot;Oh he&#x27;s changed the date on his computer&quot;
but it&#x27;s really nothing at all intelligent on my part.
Simply thanks to the hacker known as <em>View Page Source</em>,
I can reveal that it actually has a defined ordered list of words in plain text in
its source code.</p><p>I searched for the word for today in the source and noticed that
the previous words for the past few days were right there too, so
it was pretty clear that it indexing into this array of words based
on date. While the code itself was minified, it was pretty straightforward
to look for uses of the array and deduce the method.</p><p>So without further ado, here&#x27;s the ultimate strategy for completing wordle
every day: <strong>cheating</strong>.</p><div></div>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Peter R. Spackman</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/peterspackman</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://www.prs.wiki/blog/welcome"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the blog section. Not much to see yet, but I plan on actually posting on here from time to time.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the blog section. Not much to see yet, but I plan on actually posting on here from time to time.</p><p>This site is a mix of my personal site, and a wiki for me to write notes and equations related to my research
in a publicly accessible way.</p><p>Partly so I have something to point people to for exposition, but mostly for my own reference and amusement.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Peter R. Spackman</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/peterspackman</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>